

Profile

My name is Titipong Chotjit, Pank is my nick name and I'm 29 Years old.

IT System and Maintenance with 2 years+ of experience in Network and CCTV system, escalation Support, network admin and system admin. Quick solutions to technical problems, problems of IT solution.

Contact



098-276-5190



L.chotjit@outlook.com



www.facebook.com/pkinux



github.com/pkinux-titipong



www.youtube.com/@pkinux



139 Nonpattana, Borkeaw, Nakhu, Kalasin 46160

Skills

System, Network, Hardware

Inside Wiring, Cat5, Cat6 cable, install wireless, cctv device. Install Rack and managing cable, Install Network equipment. Network Technologies, Huawei Router, Switch, AP. Hikvision Switch POE, IP camera. Ethernet, Fast Ethernet, Fiber optic. WAN, LAN, TCP/IP, VLAN, VPN, IP Scan.

• Sorvor

Virtualbox, VMware, Linux server, CentOS,Ubuntu. Linux Command.

Programming

Basic python, C, JAVA, PHP, HTML, CSS programming. Basic SQL(MySQL), Database, Data Structure. Basic Backend Using Node.js.

Other

 Using hand tools. Working at height. Using fiber optic splicer.

TITIPONG CHOTJIT

IT SUPPORT, SYSTEM ENGINEER.

Education

(FEB 2021)

SUKHOTHAI THAMMATHIRAT OPEN UNIVERSITY.

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, GPA 2.44

Experience

(May 2021 - Oct 2022)

FLASH EXPRESS

IT SYSTEM AND MAINTENANCE

- Supported direct solution for computer problems. Diagnostic test and maintenance of computer equipment. Explained IT issues to nontechnical staff. identifying, diagnosing, and resolving network problems. Supporting Microsoft technologies such as Microsoft Windows, And Microsoft Office.
- Managing the installation of local area network and internet system.
 Managing the installation of cctv, cctv system. Managing the network infrastructure.
- Configuring Huawei Routers, Switches, Firewall, and Access point.
 Configuring Mikrotik Router, and Switches. Configuring Unifi Switches, and Access point.
- Monitoring network performance.

(Nov 2022 - Apr 2023)

บริษัท ขอนแก่น เซรามิค จำกัด

IT SUPPORT

- Support User for Computer, 30 user.
- Support Network System.
 Firewall, LAN, WAN, Wireless LAN.
- Support User for ERP System (Microsoft BC 365)
- Audit Document
- Programming C# to connect a floor scale by RS232 cable.

(May 2023 - FEB 2024)

RUNERGY PV TECHNOLOGY THAILAND

IT Engineer

- Support User for Computer, Printer, Internet.
- Fix IT problem such a computer, internet, printer.
- Find a network problem and sent it to Network Engineer fix.
- Install OS Like, Windows 10 Pro, Windows 11 Pro.
- Join Windows to Domain controller.
- Install security application like IP-guard.
- Install OS VM System like HCI sangfor in Dell EMC.
- Raid configuration in Dell EMC Using Boss controller card.
- Install Microsoft Office. and support when key show unlicensed.
- Monitoring System using Zabbix
- Setup network printer.



Profile

My name is Titipong Chotjit, Pank is my nick name and I'm 29 Years old.

IT System and Maintenance with 2 years+ of experience in Network and CCTV system, escalation Support, network admin and system admin. Quick solutions to technical problems, problems of IT solution.

Contact



098-276-5190



L.chotjit@outlook.com



www.facebook.com/pkinux



github.com/pkinux-titipong



www.youtube.com/@pkinux



139 Nonpattana, Borkeaw, Nakhu, Kalasin 46160

Skills

Inside Wiring, Cat5, Cat6 cable, install wireless, cctv device. Install Rack and managing cable. Install Network

System, Network, Hardware

managing cable, Install Network equipment. Network Technologies, Huawei Router, Switch, AP. Hikvision Switch POE, IP camera. Ethernet, Fast Ethernet, Fiber optic. WAN, LAN, TCP/IP, VLAN, VPN, IP Scan.

Server

Virtualbox, VMware, Linux server, CentOS,Ubuntu. Linux Command.

Programming

Basic python, C, JAVA, PHP, HTML, CSS programming. Basic SQL(MySQL), Database, Data Structure. Basic Backend Using Node.js.

Other
Using hand tools.Working at height. Using fiber optic splicer.

TITIPONG CHOTJIT

IT SUPPORT, SYSTEM ENGINEER.

Experience Conn.

(Mar 2024 - Present)

บริษัท ดูไอที โซลูชั่น จำกัด

IT SUPPORT and Consultant

- Support User as IT Consultant for 5 site
- Planning new Network system for customer
- Planning new CCTV system for customer
- Planning maintenance for customer requirements
- Planning to change some part of IT equipment for customer